Guide to the Music Department Records: Series 3, Concert Programs, 1863-[ongoing]
Music Department Records: Series 3, Concert Programs, 1863-[ongoing]
- Series 3. Concert Programs, 1878-[ongoing]
  - General Concerts
    - December 19, 1972: In Concert, performed by Wesleyan Madrigal Singers, Ilene Goldstein, David Leisner (Box 3)
    - January 28, 1973: Xylophonia, performed by Robert Becker, Michael Holmes, Anthony Levin, Steven Gadd (Box 3)
    - February 1, 1973: Philip Prince, Organist, performed by Philip Prince (Box 3)
    - February 2, 1973: No title, performed by Richard Donohue, Raymond Rendall (Box 3)
    - February 11, 1973: An Evening of Medieval, Renaissance and Baroque Music, performed by Not specified in program (Box 3)
    - February 12, 1973: A Concert of Mid-Eastern Music, performed by George Mgrdichian, Mohamed El-Akad, Edmund Jouseph (Box 3)
    - February 23, 1973: The Mikado, performed by Assorted Wesleyan Students (Box 3)
    - March 3, 1973: Ludwig van Beethoven, performed by Wesleyan Univeristy Orchestra, Wesleyan University Concert Choir (Box 3)
    - March 4, 1973: Lyceum Musicum, performed by Robert Royce, Janel Farrar, Christine Johnson Lym, Howard Lapidus, Sally Smith (Box 3)
    - March 5, 1973: Jack Hennigan, Organist, performed by Jack Hennigan (Box 3)
    - March 11, 1973: A Classical Guitar Recital, performed by David Leisner (Box 3)
    - March 13, 1973: Ilene Goldstein, Pianist, performed by Ilene Goldstein (Box 3)
    - March 18, 1973: The Classical Vocal Music of South India, performed by L. Shankar, Ramnad V. Raghavan, Bob Leroy (Box 3)
    - March 18, 1973: Teresa Gerz, Piano, performed by Teresa Gerz (Box 3)
    - March 22, 1973: Joel Andrews, performed by Joel Andrews (Box 3)
    - April 14, 1973: An Evening of Javanese Music and Dance, performed by Sumarsam, Urip Sri Maeny, and their students (Box 3)
    - April 15, 1973: Chamber Music Recital, performed by Not specified in program (Box 3)
    - April 21, 1973: A Concert, performed by Jon Barlow, Isaac Hurwitz (Box 3)
    - April 22, 1973: Marcus Thompson, Viola and Viola D'Amore, performed by Marcus Thompson (Box 3)
    - April 29, 1973: A Concert of Brass Ensemble Music, performed by Wesleyan Brass Quintet, Trombone Trio Group (Box 3)
    - April 30, 1973: Music for Flute and Piano, performed by Jon Barlow, Keith Underwood (Box 3)
    - May 3, 1973: Sankyoku: A Concert of Classical Japanese Music, performed by Students of Mrs. Ayano Ichimura and Mr. Jodo Tanaka (Box 3)
    - May 5, 1973: A Recital, performed by Mary Wayne Bush, Judith (Box 3)
    - May 6, 1973: No title, performed by William Klenz, Peter Armstrong (Box 3)
    - May 9, 1973: Bach and Son with Mozart, performed by Students and Faculty (Box 3)
    - May 11, 1973: An Afternoon of Traditional African Drumming and Dance with Mbira and Flute, performed by Abraham Adzenyah, Asante Darkwa, Freeman Donkor, Paul Berliner (Box 3)
    - May 13, 1973: A Recital, performed by Adam Dydak (Box 3)
    - May 13, 1973: A Recital, performed by Martin Plotkin, Mike Lubin (Box 3)
    - May 14, 1973: Music for Violin and Piano, performed by David Plettner, Karen Kawaguchi (Box 3)
    - May 16, 1973: The Wesleyan Madrigal Singers, performed by Wesleyan Madrigal Singers (Box 3)
    - May 20, 1973: Concert, performed by George Barth (Box 3)
    - September 26, 1973: Klaus-Christhart Kratzenstein, Organist, performed by Kluas-Christhart Kratzenstein (Box 3)
    - September 30, 1973: No title, performed by Sharon deFremery, Philip DeFremery (Box 3)
    - October 5, 1973: A Concert of Javanese Music and Dance, performed by Professors Sumarsam, Urip Sri Maeny, Oemartopo, and their students (Box 3)
    - October 5, 1973: A Wayang Kulit, performed by Professors Sumarsam, Oemartopo, Frederick deBoer, and their students (Box 3)
    - October 5, 1973: Kayan, performed by Not specified in program (Box 3)
    - October 6, 1973: As Part of the World Music Festival, performed by Vijaya Prabhakar, Malini Seshadri, Ramnad V. Raghavan (Box 3)
    - October 6, 1973: North Indian Music Concert, performed by Laxmi G. Tewari, Sharda Sashi, Carolyn Y. Tewari (Box 3)
    - October 7, 1973: The Little Earth Band, performed by Wesleyan Students (Box 3)
    - October 7, 1973: A Concert of Classical Japanese Music, performed by Namino Torii, Shudo Yamato, and their students (Box 3)
    - October 7-8, 1973: A Pow-Wow, performed by Thunderbird American Indian Dancers and Singers (Box 3)
    - October 15, 1973: South Indian Concert, performed by Not specified in program (Box 3)
    - October 18, 1973: Philip Prince, Organist, performed by Philip Prince (Box 3)
    - October 26-27, 1973: Cosi Fan Tutte, performed by Students of Wesleyan University (Box 3)
    - November 1, 1973: North Indian Music Concert, performed by V. G. Jog (Box 3)
    - November 2, 1973: South Indian Music Concert, performed by L. Shankar, R. V. Raghavan, Jeff Fuller (Box 3)
    - November 6, 1973: William Moraldo playing recorded examples of his works, performed by William Moraldo (Box 3)
    - November 6, 1973: North Indian Music Concert, performed by Moni-Lal Nag, Anil Palit (Box 3)
    - November 7, 1973: Violin Recital, performed by Richard Coff (Box 3)
    - November 10, 1973: Fall Concert, performed by Concert Choir - Schola Cantorum (Box 3)
    - November 11, 1973: Piano Recital, performed by Teresa Gerz (Box 3)
    - November 14, 1973: Organ Recital, performed by Charles Krigbaum (Box 3)
    - November 15, 1973: The Kerala Kalamandalam Kathakali Company in the Mahabharata, performed by Kerala Kalamandalam Kathakali Company (Box 3)
    - November 16, 1973: A Concert of Javanese Music, performed by Not specified in program (Box 3)
    - November 18, 1971: Music at the Honors College, performed by Marsha Hogan, Elaine Compotrone, Myron Lutzke (Box 3)
    - November 30, 1971: A Concert of Classical Japanese Music, performed by Sankyoku (Box 3)
    - December 4, 1973: Piano Recital, performed by Adalovni (Box 3)
    - December 6, 1973: Indonesian Music and Dance Concert, performed by Susarsam, Urip Sri Maeny, and their students (Box 3)
    - December 7, 1973: Concert of Electronic Music, performed by Alvin Lucier and his students (Box 3)
    - December 10, 1973: Student Recital, performed by Wesleyan students (Box 3)
    - December 11, 1973: Piano Recital, performed by Rita Gottlieb (Box 3)
    - December 12, 1973: South Indian Music Concert, performed by L. Shankar, L. Subramaniam (Box 3)
    - December 14, 1973: Concert of African Drumming and Dance with Flute, performed by Abraham Adzenyah, Asante Darkwa, Freeman Donkor (Box 3)
    - December 15, 1973: Candlelight Concert, performed by Not specified in program (Box 3)
    - December 16, 1973: Candlelight Concert, performed by Not specified in program (Box 3)
    - February 3, 1974: Music at the Honors College, performed by Michael Haber, Orin Grossman (Box 3)
    - February 10, 1974: Organ Recital, performed by David Dunkle (Box 3)
    - February 19, 1974: Piano Recital, performed by Rita Sloan Gottlieb (Box 3)
    - February 22, 1974: Evening of Seneca Music, performed by Avery Jimerson (Box 3)
    - February 24, 1974: An Evening with John Cage, performed by John Cage (Box 3)
    - March 3, 1974: Recital, performed by Lanny Paykin, Marian Hahn (Box 3)
    - March 5, 1974: North Indian Music Concert, performed by Steve Gorn, Shardi Sahai (Box 3)
    - March 5 (or 6), 1974: Winter Concert, performed by Concert Choir, Richard Donohue (Box 3)
    - March 10, 1974: Concert Performance, performed by Wesleyan Orchestra, Isaac Hurwitz, Jon Barlow (Box 3)
    - March 12, 1974: North Indian Music Concert, performed by Krishna Sanyal, Shardi Sahai (Box 3)
    - March 13, 1974: Tokyo String Quartet, performed by Koichiro Harada, Kazuhide Isomura, Yoshiko Nakura, Sadao Harada (Box 3)
    - March 15, 1974: Kantamoto Dance TroupeAn Evening of Traditional African Drumming and Dance, performed by Kantamoto Dance Troupe (Box 3)
    - March 17, 1974: Music and Dance Recital, performed by Stephanie Woodard, Peter Zummo (Box 3)
    - March 19, 1974: Piano Recital, performed by Adam Dydak (Box 3)
    - March 20, 1974: Oboe Recital, performed by Scott Brodie (Box 3)
    - April 7, 1974: Piano Recital, performed by Julia Johnson (Box 3)
    - April 9, 1974: A Concert of Classical Japanese Music, performed by Namino Torii, et al. (Box 3)
    - April 10, 1974: Peter Day, Sue Day, and New Haven Scottish Country Dances, performed by Peter & Sue Day, et al. (Box 3)
    - April 14, 1974: Music for a while, performed by Judith Davidoff, et al. (Box 3)
    - April 14, 1974: Schola Cantorum, performed by Schola Cantorum (Box 3)
    - April 19, 1974: A Concert of Javanese Music and Dance, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - April 19, 1974: Wanda Boykin, performed by Wanda Boykin, The Afro-American Performance Ensemble (Box 3)
    - April 23, 1974: Ilene Goldstein, Pianist, performed by Ilene Goldstein (Box 3)
    - April 21, 1974: A Recital by William Henry and Justin Blasdale, performed by William Henry, Justin Blasdale (Box 3)
    - April 26, 1974: African Drum and Dance Concert, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - May 1, 1974: A Concert of Classical Japanese Music, performed by The students of Namino Torii and Shudo Yamato (Box 3)
    - May 5, 1974: Neil Keen, Organist, performed by Neil Keen (Box 3)
    - May 5, 1974: A Concert for Shakuhachi Solo, performed by Kinko-Ryu Honkyoku (Box 3)
    - May 8, 1974: Both pieces are products of a composition tutorial with Richard Winslow., performed by Andre Barbera, Abbie Horwitz, et al. (Box 3)
    - May 9, 1974: A Piano Recital, performed by Dane Waterman (Box 3)
    - May 14, 1974: Recital, performed by John McLucas, Sherrie Smith (Box 3)
    - September 6, 1974: The Baroque Festival Orchestra, performed by The Baroque Festival Orchestra, Robert Conant (Box 3)
    - September 15, 1974: Music at the Honors College, performed by Elizabeth Rich (Box 3)
    - October 24, 1974: Linda Clark, Organist, performed by Linda Clark (Box 3)
    - October 26, 1974: Fall Concert, performed by The Concert Choir and Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - November 7, 1974: James Fulkerson, Trombone, performed by James Fulkerson (Box 3)
    - November 15, 1974: Sankyoku: A Concert of Classical Japanese Music, performed by Namino Torii, Shudo Yamato (Box 3)
    - November 17, 1974: Music for the Oboe, performed by Cornelia Bodine, et al. (Box 3)
    - November 21, 1974: Charles Krigbaum, Organist, performed by Charles Krigbaum (Box 3)
    - November 22, 1974: Elly Ameling, Soprano, performed by Elly Ameling, Dalton Baldwin (Box 3)
    - November 23, 1974: Wesleyan Composers I, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - November 24, 1974: The Wesleyan Orchestra, performed by The Wesleyan Orchestra, Isaac Hurwitz (Box 3)
    - December 2, 1974: Some Anniversaries, performed by Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - December 4, 1974: Some Anniversaries, performed by Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - January 23, 1975: Johannes-Ernst Kohler, Organist, performed by Johannes-Ernst Kohler (Box 3)
    - January 26, 1975: Peter Standaart, Flute, performed by Peter Standaart, Larry Todd, Garrett Bennett (Box 3)
    - February 1, 1975: Endgame, performed by Jack Bittner, et al. (Box 3)
    - March 16, 1975: Sherrie Smith, Pianist, performed by Sherrie Smith (Box 3)
    - Undated: New Music for Voice and Diverse Instruments, performed by Geordie Arnold, George Barth, et al. (Box 3)
    - April 1, 1975: Kresna Kembang, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - April 8, 1975: Teresa Escandon, Pianist, performed by Teresa Escandon (Box 3)
    - April 9, 1975: Neil Keen, Organist, performed by Neil Keen (Box 3)
    - April 11, 1975: A Concert of New Music from the Wesleyan University Electronic Studio, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - April 12, 1975: Dartmouth Presents New Music from Wesleyan University, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - April 13, 1975: The Wesleyan Asian Students Party, performed by Theresa Teng Chen, Robert Wallace (Box 3)
    - April 13, 1975: Peter Armstrong, Pianist, performed by Peter Armstrong (Box 3)
    - April 18, 1975: A Concert of Experimental Music, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - April 19, 1975: Gregory Bonenberger, Guitarist, performed by Gregory Bonenberger (Box 3)
    - April 24, 1975: Music of David Behrman, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - April 25, 1975: The Concert Choir, performed by Concert Choir, Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - April 27, 1975: A Double Bass Recital, performed by Sarah Kendall (Box 3)
    - May 2, 1975: An Evening of Chamber Music, performed by Charles Tabony, Harry Clark, Sanda Schuldmann (Box 3)
    - May 2, 1975: A Concert of Classical Japanese Music, performed by Namino Torii, Shudo Yamato (Box 3)
    - May 6, 1975: Informal Student Organ Recital, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - May 9, 1975: An Evening of Traditional African Drumming, Flute, and Dance, performed by Abraham Adzenyah, S. D. Asiama, Freeman Donkor, and their students (Box 3)
    - May 1, 1975: Music of the Baroque, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - April 9, 1976: Music for Violin and Piano by Charles Ives and Carl Ruggles, performed by Daniel Stepner, John Kirkpatrick (Box 3)
    - September 17, 1976: Michael Lorimer, Classical Guitarist, performed by Michael Lorimer (Box 3)
    - October 29, 1976: The Fires of London, performed by Peter Maxwell Davies (Box 3)
    - October 22nd and 23, 1976: Three Centuries of American Music, performed by Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - November 12, 1976: Programs from the 17th Century, performed by Jean Hakes, James Weaver (Box 3)
    - December 4, 1976: Mostly Baroque, performed by Denise Eibel, Ed Merck, Andrew Spearman (Box 3)
    - January 21, 1977: Compositions of Neely Bruce, performed by Neely Bruce, et al. (Box 3)
    - January 28, 1977: Teresa Escandon, Pianist, performed by Teresa Escandon (Box 3)
    - February 11, 1977: The Chamber Orchestra of New England, performed by James Sinclair (Box 3)
    - February 27, 1977: Flute & Piano Recital, performed by Peter Standaart, Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - March 1, 1977: American Women Composers: A Recital of Songs, performed by Neely Bruce, et al. (Box 3)
    - March 2, 1977: Music for Bassoon & Friends, performed by Garrett Bennett, et al. (Box 3)
    - March 3, 1977: A Concert of West African Dance & Drumming, performed by Abraham Adzenyah and the Wesleyan African Drumming Ensemble (Box 3)
    - March 7, 1977: A Concert of Classical Japanese Music, performed by Namino Torii, Ryudow Takahashi (Box 3)
    - March 5 and 9, 1977: Romantic Music for Chorus and Winds, performed by Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - March 8, 1977: Elyse Topalian, Pianist, performed by Elyse Topalian (Box 3)
    - April 2-3, 1977: Rose Moon, performed by Neely Bruce, et al. (Box 3)
    - April 5, 1977: A Duo Piano Concert, performed by George Barth, Dane Waterman (Box 3)
    - April 6, 1977: Wesleyan Big Band, performed by Bill Barron, et al. (Box 3)
    - April 7-8, 1977: Wesleyan Orchestra Concert, performed by Wesleyan Orchestra, R. K. Winslow (Box 3)
    - April 11, 1977: Classical Guitar Recital, performed by Jeff Clair (Box 3)
    - April 15, 1977: A Concert of South Indian Music, performed by T. Viswanathan, K. Subramanian, T. Ranganathan (Box 3)
    - April 16, 1977: Original Jazz Compositions, performed by Susan Davis, et al. (Box 3)
    - April 19, 1977: Nesumen, performed by Kathy Bergeron, et al. (Box 3)
    - April 23, 1977: An Evening of Japanese Music & Dance, performed by The Wesleyan Gamelon, R. M. Soekanto, et al. (Box 3)
    - April 27, 1977: New Works by Marc Grafe, performed by Marc Grafe, et al. (Box 3)
    - April 29, 1977: Sankyoku Onshukai, performed by The students of Namino Torii and Ryudow Takahashi (Box 3)
    - April 30, 1977: Original 20th Century Wind Music, performed by Wesleyan Symphonic Wind Ensemble, Ed Merck (Box 3)
    - May 3, 1977: Informal Student Organ Recital, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - May 3, 1977: David Leisner, Guitarist, performed by David Leisner (Box 3)
    - May 4, 1977: West African Dance Music, performed by The Wesleyan Ghanaian (Box 3)
    - May 6-7, 1977: Israel in Egypt, performed by The Concert Choir, Wesleyan Singers, The Wesleyan Orchestra, Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - April 28 and May 8, 1977: Jacobean Music for Voices and Viols, performed by Quidam Musici (Box 3)
    - May 8, 1977: Dane Waterman, Piano, performed by Dane Waterman (Box 3)
    - May 9, 1977: Philip Prince, Organist, performed by Philip Prince (Box 3)
    - May 10, 1977: Vocal Recital, performed by Frederick Black, Neil Stannard (Box 3)
    - May 11, 1977: Music for Clarinet & Piano, performed by W. Thomas Ridenour, et al. (Box 3)
    - May 13, 1977: A Recital at Russel House, performed by Gail Gimbel, David Anderson (Box 3)
    - May 14, 1977: Wesleyan Composers Concert, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - May 15, 1977: Cello Music, performed by Eliot Bailen, Tim Fuller, Sharon Wahl (Box 3)
    - May 17, 1977: Chamber Music Recital, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - September 16, 1977: Titleless, performed by Harry Clark, Sanda Schuldmann (Box 3)
    - September 17, 1977: The Burlle Marx Trio, performed by Barbara Westphal, Madalena Burle Marx, James Swisher (Box 3)
    - September 21, 1977: Teresa Escandon, Pianist, performed by Teresa Escandon (Box 3)
    - September 23, 1977: Guarneri String Quartet, performed by Arnold Steinhardt, John Dalley, Michael Tree, David Soyer (Box 3)
    - October 4, 1977: The University of Illinois Contemporary Chamber Players, performed by The University of Illinois Contemporary Chamber Players (Box 3)
    - October 6, 1977: John Schaeffer, Organist, performed by John Schaeffer (Box 3)
    - October 7, 1977: Sankyoku, performed by Namino Torii, et al. (Box 3)
    - October 12, 1977: Navaratri Celebration: A Concert of Bharata Natyam, performed by Kay Poursine, et al. (Box 3)
    - October 16, 1977: Britt Wheeler, Harpsichord, performed by Britt Wheeler (Box 3)
    - October 19, 1977: Compositions of Neely Bruce, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - November 4, 1977: New Music by John Cage, performed by Greg Sultan, Paul Zukofsky (Box 3)
    - November 10, 1977: Roy Horton, Organ, performed by Roy Horton, et al. (Box 3)
    - November 11, 1977: The Wesleyan Orchestra: A Concert of Works by Rossini, Bach, Mussorgsky, & Schubert, performed by The Wesleyan Orchestra (Box 3)
    - November 13, 1977: Music as Theatre, performed by Elliot Schwartz (Box 3)
    - November 13, 1977: Student Performance Workshop I, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - November 14, 1977: Experimental Music by Nicolas Collins, performed by Nicolas Collins, et al. (Box 3)
    - November 18, 1977: Wesleyan Big Band, performed by Bill Barron, et al. (Box 3)
    - November 20, 1977: Student Performance Workshiop II, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - December 2, 1977: Student Recital of Japanese Music, performed by The students of Namino Torii and Reihi Sano (Box 3)
    - December 3, 1977: An Evening of Javanese Music and Dance, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - December 4, 1977: Wesleyan Students' Recital, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - December 6, 1977: Wesleyan Wind Quintet, performed by Peter Standaart, Peter Stempe, Thomas Ridenour, Andrew Spearman, Garrett Bennett (Box 3)
    - December 10, 1977: Candlelight Concert, performed by Richard Winslow, Wesleyan University Concert Choir and Orchestra (Box 3)
    - December 15, 1977: Nesumen, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - January 20, 1978: A Concert of South Indian Music, performed by Jon B. Higgins, T. Viswanathan, T. S. Sankaran, Jody Cormack, Winnie Lockwood (Box 3)
    - January 27, 1978: Michael Lorimer, Classical Guitarist & Baroque Guitarist, performed by Michael Lorimer (Box 3)
    - January 30, 1978: New Music from China, performed by Siu-Hang Lai, Euphemia Lai, Sun-Mon Chan (Box 3)
    - February 1, 1978: Saxophone Recital, performed by Peter Saiano, Paul Klein (Box 3)
    - February 4, 1978: Piano Recital, performed by George Barth (Box 3)
    - February 5, 1978: Music at the Honors College, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - February 12, 1978: Rose Moon, performed by Neely Bruce, Wesleyan Singers (Box 3)
    - February 15, 1978: Violin & Piano Recital, performed by Barbara Westphal, James Swisher (Box 3)
    - February 18, 1978: Senior Recital, performed by Julia Scolnik, Tim Fuller, Cheung Wai Lang (Box 3)
    - February 19, 1978: Music at the Honors College: Lieder by Hugo Wolf, performed by Stephen Crites, Marion Irizarry (Box 3)
    - February 22, 1978: Middle Eastern Music: A Concert for 'Ud and Drum, performed by Khamis Ali El Fino, Aziza Ali, Israel Ross (Box 3)
    - February 23, 1978: Charles Krigbaum, Organist, performed by Charles Krigbaum (Box 3)
    - March 3, 1978: A Concert of South Indian Music, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - March 5, 1978: Music at the Honors College, performed by Gregory Bonenberger, Geofrey Bonenberger (Box 3)
    - March 9, 1978: Wesleyan Orchestra, performed by Wesleyan Orchestra, Roger Solie (Box 3)
    - March 29, 1978: Oboe Recital: Peter Stempe, performed by Peter Stempe, et al. (Box 3)
    - March 30, 1978: Frans Brueggen, Virtuoso Recorder, performed by Frans Brueggen (Box 3)
    - April 1, 1978: Violin Recital: Peter Sacco, performed by Peter Sacco, Virginia Weckstrom (Box 3)
    - April 4, 1978: Inanna's Descent into the Netherworld, performed by Beth Skinner, et al. (Box 3)
    - April 5, 1978: Nameless, performed by Wesleyan Big Band, Bill Barron, Various (Box 3)
    - April 7-8, 1978: Wesleyan Singers, performed by Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - April 14, 1978: Tashi, performed by Peter Serkin, Ida Kavafian, Richard Stoltzman (Box 3)
    - April 16, 1978: An Evening of Javanese Court Gamelan Music, performed by Wesleyan Gamelan Ensemble, R. M. Soekanto S. Darsono (Box 3)
    - April 16, 1978: Lenora Sampson Williams; Honors Thesis Voice Recital, performed by Lenora Sampson Williams (Box 3)
    - April 17, 1978: Tom Ross, performed by Tom Ross (Box 3)
    - April 19, 1978: A Concert of South Indian Vocal Music, performed by Winthrop Lockwood, John Freudenheim, Jody Cormack, Guy Pugh (Box 3)
    - April 21, 1978: By a stroke of luck, the Korean dancer Ae-Ju Cho is visiting and has agreed to do a brief program, performed by Ae-Ju Cho (Box 3)
    - April 21, 1978: An Evening of West African Music and Dance, performed by Abraham K. Adzinyah and his students (Box 3)
    - April 22, 1978: Tracks: An Aural Environment in Motion, performed by Ms. K. Ford Gates (Box 3)
    - April 23, 1978: Wesleyan Wind Ensemble, performed by Wesleyan Wind Ensemble, Thomas Ridenour (Box 3)
    - April 23, 1978: Piano Recital, performed by Helen Riess (Box 3)
    - April 24, 1978: Original Compositions by Gretchen A. Bilson, performed by Gretchen A. Bilson, et al. (Box 3)
    - April 25, 1978: Music by T. Kosugi, performed by Takehisa Kosugi, et al. (Box 3)
    - April 26, 1978: Quartet for the End of Time by Aliver Messiaen, performed by George Barth, Ann Rylands, Mary Lou Rylands, Tom Ridenour (Box 3)
    - April 27, 1978: Richard Konzen, Organist, performed by Richard Konzen (Box 3)
    - April 28-29, 1978: The Creation, Oratorio by Joseph Haydn, performed by The Concert Choir, The Wesleyan Orchestra, guest artists, Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - May 4-5, 1978: Festival of Indonesian Performance, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - May 9, 1978: Informal Student Organ Recital, performed by Joseph Dow, Bradford Wells, Beth Solowey (Box 3)
    - May 11, 1978: Gala Concert of the Mattabassett Ethiopiano Melodists, performed by Peter Hall, Neely Bruce, et al. (Box 3)
    - September 19, 1978: Garrick Ohlsson, Piano, performed by Garrick Ohlsson (Box 3)
    - September 29, 1978: Sankyoku, performed by Namino Torii, Reihi Sano, Tono Ozaki, Eino Nakagawa (Box 3)